<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><labels locale="en">
<label key="1879064034" value="Champion"/>
<label key="1879064035" value="Captain"/>
<label key="1879064036" value="Minstrel"/>
<label key="1879064037" value="Lore-master"/>
<label key="1879064038" value="Guardian"/>
<label key="1879064039" value="Burglar"/>
<label key="1879064040" value="Hunter"/>
<label key="1879104865" value="Rune-keeper"/>
<label key="1879107697" value="Warden"/>
<label key="1879306744" value="Beorning"/>
<label key="1879409409" value="Brawler"/>
<label key="1879458225" value="Mariner"/>
<label key="key:620768662:209557171" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Class Difficulty:&lt;/rgb&gt; Basic&lt;/li&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Role:&lt;/rgb&gt; Damage&lt;/li&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Gameplay:&lt;/rgb&gt; Champions wade into battle swinging their weapons in all directions, dealing significant damage to many foes at once. With each strike their Fervour grows, allowing them to use even more potent skills. Special stances may be used to greatly increase damage dealt at the cost of defence or enhance defence at the cost of damage. In fellowships, a Champion concentrates on engaging as many foes as possible.&lt;/li&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Lore:&lt;/rgb&gt; Unrelenting in battle, Champions are the consummate warriors. A Champion cares not for his own well-being, but relies on his strength and prowess to slay the Enemy before they can bring more destruction to Middle-earth.&#10;&#10;This class is inspired by Gimli son of Glóin, whose skill in arms matched the bow-skills of Legolas.&lt;/li&gt;"/>
<label key="key:620768705:209557171" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Class Difficulty:&lt;/rgb&gt; Moderate&lt;/li&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Role:&lt;/rgb&gt; Support&lt;/li&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Gameplay:&lt;/rgb&gt; Captains are armoured melee fighters and masters of buffing; skills that enhance allies. They may summon a Herald companion to fight by their side, ensuring they always have an ally to buff. They can also Mark foes, giving benefits to all who attack them. In fellowships, a Captain supports his allies with healing and buffs, while still dealing respectable damage.&lt;/li&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Lore:&lt;/rgb&gt; The Captains of Middle-earth hold the future in their hands. By their own strength of arms and the inspiration they instill in others, they must lead the Free Peoples to victory.&#10;&#10;This class is inspired by Eärnur, last King of Gondor, who was revered both as a captain skilled in arms and as a lore-master.&lt;/li&gt;"/>
<label key="key:620768726:209557171" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Class Difficulty:&lt;/rgb&gt; Moderate&lt;/li&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Role:&lt;/rgb&gt; Healer&lt;/li&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Gameplay:&lt;/rgb&gt; Minstrels are known for their healing abilities and are capable of dealing respectable damage with War-speech.  They have a variety of support skills and special Ballads. Using a Ballad unlocks more potent Ballads, which culminate with powerful Anthems. In fellowships, a Minstrel keeps his allies healed and supported.&lt;/li&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Lore:&lt;/rgb&gt; Middle-earth is a land deeply infused with music, and true Minstrels are skilled at tapping into that power. They weave songs and tales so stirring that their companions' morale will not fail, and they will be driven to perform greater feats of prowess. They can even utter words of true power and ward against the forces of darkness with their Anthems.&#10;&#10;This class was inspired by Lúthien Tinúviel, whose Elven voice beguiled friend and foe alike.&lt;/li&gt;"/>
<label key="key:620768749:209557171" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Class Difficulty:&lt;/rgb&gt; Advanced&lt;/li&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Role:&lt;/rgb&gt; Damage, Support&lt;/li&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Gameplay:&lt;/rgb&gt; Lore-masters are the masters of the natural world. They combine arcane knowledge of the elements with a quick wit to skillfully overcome most any obstacle. They may call on animal companions to fight by their side or use elaborate concoctions to turn the fury of nature on their foes. In fellowships, a Lore-master is equally capable of wielding the natural world against their enemies as they are supporting their allies, through healing and by disrupting their enemies' capacity to fight.&lt;/li&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Lore:&lt;/rgb&gt; Lore-masters are seekers of knowledge and the guardians of wisdom. Through study of bygone Ages, they learn ancient secrets that allow them to hinder foes, as well as protect against the dark powers of the Enemy.&#10;&#10;This class was inspired by Elrond Halfelven, Elf-lord and Master of Rivendell.&lt;/li&gt;"/>
<label key="key:620768766:209557171" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Class Difficulty:&lt;/rgb&gt; Basic&lt;/li&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Role:&lt;/rgb&gt; Defence&lt;/li&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Gameplay:&lt;/rgb&gt; Guardians wear heavy armour and have many defensive skills that allow them to survive battles against the most fearsome foes. Guardians also have skills that draw foes' attention away from their allies and to themselves.   In fellowships, a Guardian forces enemies to attack himself, so his more fragile allies will not be harmed by the foes.&lt;/li&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Lore:&lt;/rgb&gt; The Guardians are the stout protectors of the weak and defenders of those in need, loyal companions to the end. True Guardians stand to the forefront of battle, shielding their allies from enemy assaults.&#10;&#10;This class was inspired by the hobbit Samwise Gamgee, whose loyalty to Frodo Baggins knew no bounds.&lt;/li&gt;"/>
<label key="key:620768787:209557171" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Class Difficulty:&lt;/rgb&gt; Advanced&lt;/li&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Role:&lt;/rgb&gt; Support&lt;/li&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Gameplay:&lt;/rgb&gt; Burglars are masters of debuffing; skills that cause foes to deal less damage or be easier to kill. They utilize their Trick skills to debuff foes and can later remove the Tricks for additional benefits. Burglars also have Stealth skills and are proficient at initiating Fellowship Manoeuvres. In fellowships, a Burglar supports his allies by debuffing foes, while dealing respectable damage.&lt;/li&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Lore:&lt;/rgb&gt; Burglars are masters of stealth and misdirection. They rely on sleight-of-hand and startling attacks that allow their companions to overwhelm adversaries.&#10;&#10;This class is inspired by the famous Bilbo Baggins, who accompanied Thorin and Company on their quest to the Lonely Mountain.&lt;/li&gt;"/>
<label key="key:620768801:209557171" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Class Difficulty:&lt;/rgb&gt; Basic&lt;/li&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Role:&lt;/rgb&gt; Damage, Support&lt;/li&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Gameplay:&lt;/rgb&gt; Hunters are proficient at dealing significant damage to a single foe at long range.  Their basic bow skills generate Focus, allowing them to use even more potent skills.  If a foe manages to close into melee, the Hunter's dual-wielded weapons are capable of dealing the final blow.  In fellowships, a Hunter concentrates on quickly killing foes one at a time.&lt;/li&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Lore:&lt;/rgb&gt; Hunters are masters of field and forest, unmatched in their dexterity with the bow. They use their survival skills to guide companions and lay traps for enemies. The coming of the Enemy has forced them to adapt these skills to use against new prey.&#10;&#10;This class was inspired by Legolas, Prince of Mirkwood, a mighty hunter and companion of Aragorn.&lt;/li&gt;"/>
<label key="key:620802471:209557171" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Class Difficulty:&lt;/rgb&gt; Moderate&lt;/li&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Role:&lt;/rgb&gt; Damage / Healer&lt;/li&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Gameplay:&lt;/rgb&gt; Rune-keepers must choose during each battle to focus on damaging skills or healing skills. Either choice will shift their Attunement, unlocking more potent skills, but restricting access to others. In addition, they have support skills that may always be used. In fellowships, a Rune-keeper keeps allies healed or deals significant damage to the foes.&lt;/li&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Lore:&lt;/rgb&gt; Rune-keepers are gifted linguists and masters of true names. With this knowledge, a Rune-keeper crafts powerful rune-words that help the Free Peoples. Through unparalleled mastery of Angerthas and Tengwar runes, a Rune-keeper evokes much more than a normal scribe.  Dagor runes deal with battle, Nestad with healing, and Thalas with support.&#10;&#10;This class is inspired by the master Elf-smith Celebrimbor, whose skill with runes of power was unparalleled.&lt;/li&gt;"/>
<label key="key:620803743:209557171" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Class Difficulty:&lt;/rgb&gt; Advanced&lt;/li&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Role:&lt;/rgb&gt; Defence&lt;/li&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Gameplay:&lt;/rgb&gt; Wardens are mobile melee combatants who use Javelins for initiating combat and against ranged foes. Their unique Warden Shields and a variety of defensive skills allow them to stay in the fight longer than most. Basic Warden skills build up their Gambit chain, which can be spent to unleash special Gambit skills. In fellowships, a Warden forces enemies to attack himself, so his more fragile allies will not be harmed by the foes.&lt;/li&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Lore:&lt;/rgb&gt; The Warden patrols the borders of civilized lands, preventing the encroachment of fell creatures from the Wild. They limit themselves to medium armour so that they can travel swiftly and silently to defend those they protect from threats. Wardens all have some military training and have mastered a style of combat that uses combinations of basic attacks to create masterful Gambits.&#10;&#10;This class was inspired by the marchwarden of Lothlórien, Haldir, and his brothers Rúmil and Orophin.&lt;/li&gt;"/>
<label key="key:620948417:209557171" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Class Difficulty:&lt;/rgb&gt; Advanced &lt;/li&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Role:&lt;/rgb&gt; Damage / Support&lt;/li&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Gameplay:&lt;/rgb&gt; Beornings are skin-changers that can change into the form of a bear in combat. They focus their wrath while in bear form, choosing to deal grievous blows or bolster their own resolve. While skilled in combat, some Beornings also choose to wield their knowledge of the wilderness to assist their allies.&lt;/li&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Lore:&lt;/rgb&gt; The Beornings of Middle-earth are a largely reclusive people. They trace their ancestry to Beorn himself and spend most of their time deep in the wilderness. The solitude of the forest gives little comfort in recent times with the enemy encroaching from all sides. The time has come for the descendants of Beorn to lend their strength to the Free Peoples of Middle-earth.&#10;&#10;This class is inspired by Beorn, who bravely stood with the Free Peoples during the Battle of Five Armies.&lt;/li&gt;"/>
<label key="key:621035448:209557171" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Class Difficulty:&lt;/rgb&gt; Advanced&lt;/li&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Role:&lt;/rgb&gt; Offence/Defence&lt;/li&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Gameplay:&lt;/rgb&gt; Brawlers are aggressive melee fighters who wield a unique resource called Mettle to maximize their damage and fuel their most powerful skills. Although their offensive capabilities truly shine in one-on-one combat, they are not without recourse when faced with multiple enemies. In fellowships, a Brawler's abrasive nature helps them hold the ire of their foes and keep their allies safe.&lt;/li&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt; Lore:&lt;/rgb&gt; Brawlers are formidable fighters whose bold manoeuvres can topple their foes and safeguard their allies.&#10;&#10;This class is inspired by Helm Hammerhand, who to the astonishment of many, would take to the battlefield bare-handed.&lt;/li&gt;"/>
<label key="key:621072108:209557171" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Class Difficulty:&lt;/rgb&gt; Advanced&lt;/li&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Role:&lt;/rgb&gt; Offence/Support&lt;/li&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Gameplay:&lt;/rgb&gt; Mariners are confident melee fighters who wield swords deftly to challenge the forces of evil. Mariners have an innate sense of the flow of combat, and use their balance to adjust their fighting style to best fit the moment. Mariners also know how to use combinations of individual movements to create powerful skill chains. In fellowships, Mariners can use shanties to coordinate and motivate their allies, as well as craft strange concoctions to confound and disrupt foes.&lt;/li&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Lore:&lt;/rgb&gt; Mariners are resourceful combatants, capable of using strange devices as well as their surroundings to aid them in battle.&#10;&#10;This class is inspired by Eärendil, who alone among men successfully sailed to the Uttermost West to plead for the aid of the Valar.&lt;/li&gt;"/>
</labels>
