<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><labels locale="en">
<label key="1" value="Mordor"/>
<label key="10" value="Grey Mountains"/>
<label key="11" value="Mirkwood"/>
<label key="12" value="The Lonely Mountain"/>
<label key="13" value="Stoor"/>
<label key="14" value="Harfoot"/>
<label key="15" value="Lindon"/>
<label key="16" value="Dale-lands"/>
<label key="17" value="Bree-land"/>
<label key="18" value="Fallohide"/>
<label key="19" value="Vales of Anduin"/>
<label key="2" value="Edhellond"/>
<label key="21" value="Beleriand"/>
<label key="22" value="Imladris"/>
<label key="23" value="Gondolin"/>
<label key="24" value="Ossiriand"/>
<label key="26" value="Nargothrond"/>
<label key="27" value="Mordor"/>
<label key="28" value="Misthallow"/>
<label key="29" value="Umbar"/>
<label key="3" value="Iron Hills"/>
<label key="30" value="Rhûn/The Khôl"/>
<label key="31" value="Harad/Shagâna"/>
<label key="4" value="Blue Mountains"/>
<label key="5" value="Rohan"/>
<label key="6" value="Gondor"/>
<label key="7" value="Rivendell"/>
<label key="8" value="Lórien"/>
<label key="9" value="White Mountains"/>
<label key="key:620757446:100924195" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Naming Guidelines: &lt;/rgb&gt;With rare exception, the Elves of Middle-earth have Sindarin names.&#10;&#10;Names like Elrond, Legolas, and Lindir are examples of Elf-men in Middle-earth.&#10;&#10;Common masculine name endings in Sindarin are -adan, -aran, -bor, -born, -dir, -dor, -had, -ion, -las, -moth, -or, -phant, -phor, -randir, -ras, -rod, -rond, -ros, -thalion, -thir, -uil, and -we. Common prefixes are Adan-, Aeg-, Am-, Aran-, Bara-, Beleg-, Celeb-, Curu-, Dag-, El-, Fela-, Fin-, Gal-, Gil-, Hal-, Ing-, Lin-, Mal-, Pen-, Tar-, Thurin-, and Ul-.&lt;/li&gt;"/>
<label key="key:620757446:102078387" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Naming Guidelines: &lt;/rgb&gt;Beornings take names influenced by Old Norse.&#10;&#10;Grimbeorn, Folhúth, and Gultoth are examples of Beorning names.&#10;&#10;Common masculine name endings for Beornings are -beorn, -bert, -brand, -gils, -mark, -fast, -geir, -har, -karl, -mar, -moth, -mund, -rath, -rek, -styr, -thorn, -vald, -var, -vat, -vir, and –vith. Common prefixes are Ag-, Ald-, Arn-, Bald-, Borg-, Both-, Dag-, Dreng-, Eld-, Forn-, Froth-, Gal-, Glum-, Guth-, Heim-, Hroth-, Is-, Jarn-, Lyth-, Moth-, Nef-, Oth-, Rath-, Rand-, Skal-, Stig-, Throt-, Vald-, and Vig-.&lt;/li&gt;"/>
<label key="key:620757446:103743475" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Naming Guidelines: &lt;/rgb&gt;With rare exception, the Elves of Middle-earth have Sindarin names.&#10;&#10;Names like Arwen, Celebrían, and Galadriel are examples of Elf-women in Middle-earth.&#10;&#10;Common feminine name endings in Sindarin are -anor, -dal, -dis, -el, -eth, -iel, -il, -gil, -los, -raen, -reth, -riel, -rian, -rien, -uilas, -uilos, -wen, and -wing. Common prefixes are Adan-, And-, Ar-, Bel-, Breg-, Celeb-, Dol-, Edhel-, El-, Fan-, Find-, Galadh-, Gil-, Hir-, Ior-, Ir-, Lal-, Mel-, Mor-, Nim-, Rod-, Sael-, and Tinu-.&lt;/li&gt;"/>
<label key="key:620757446:109680147" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Lore: &lt;/rgb&gt;You come from the Dale-lands in the north-east of Middle-earth, beneath the Lonely Mountain, where Bard the Bowman slew the dragon Smaug and fought in the Battle of Five Armies.&lt;/li&gt;"/>
<label key="key:620757446:111241971" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Naming Guidelines: &lt;/rgb&gt;River Hobbit men still use the olden names of their kind, drawing on ancient Celtic and Germanic tongues.&#10;&#10;Some examples are Athelmar, Cadvan, Gerbald, Meginard, and Rotri. Common name endings are -an, -bern, -bert, -cant, -doc, -frith, -gal, -girn, -hal, -hard, -ig, -lach -mal, -min, -noth, -ram, -red, -seth, -vald, -werth, and -win. Common prefixes are Agil-, Alb-, Amal-, Arn-, Bald-, Bern-, Broch-, Burg-, Cara-, Child-, Dud-, Ed-, Ellan-, Elu-, Era-, Fara-, Fridu-, Geb-, Glad-, Gorthi-, Gundi-, Hari-, Hil-, Ingi-, Lof-, Ludi-, Mahal-, Mer-, Mor-, Mund-, Nor-, Odal-, Ord-, Ot-, Ragin-, Rodi-, Roth-, Rudi-, Stig-, Thudi-, Udu-, Una-, Urb-, Wara-, Wido-, and Wyn-.&lt;/li&gt;"/>
<label key="key:620757446:114938019" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Naming Guidelines: &lt;/rgb&gt;With rare exception, women of Gondor have Sindarin names.&#10;&#10;Gilraen and Ioreth are examples of Gondor women's names.&#10;&#10;Common feminine name endings in Sindarin are -anor, -dal, -dis, -el, -eth, -iel, -il, -gil, -los, -raen, -riel, -rian, -rien, -uilas, -uilos, -wen, and -wing. Common prefixes are Adan-, And-, Ar-, Bel-, Breg-, Celeb-, Dol-, Edhel-, El-, Fan-, Find-, Galadh-, Gil-, Hir-, Ior-, Ir-, Lal-, Mel-, Mor-, Nim-, Rod-, Sael-, and Tinú-.&lt;/li&gt;"/>
<label key="key:620757446:118142723" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Naming Guidelines: &lt;/rgb&gt;Dwarves tend towards short, simple Norse-styled names.&#10;&#10;Common endings are -ori, -óin, -íli, -alin, -orin, -osi, -imli, and ormur, coupled with beginnings using consonants like D-, F-, G-, H-, K-, L-, M-, N-, R-, T-, Th-, and W-,  or paired consonants like Dr-, Dw-, Fl-, Gl-, or Thr-. Example are Dori, Glóin, Kíli, Balin, Thorin, Flosi, Gimli, and Gormur.&#10;&#10;A few dwarves have more complex names, combining whole words with specific endings or other whole words. (Examples: Skorgrím, Einskaldir.)&lt;/li&gt;"/>
<label key="key:620757446:118621411" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Naming Guidelines: &lt;/rgb&gt;With rare exception, the Elves of Middle-earth have Sindarin names.&#10;&#10;Names like Elrond, Legolas, and Lindir are examples of Elf-men in Middle-earth.&#10;&#10;Common masculine name endings in Sindarin are -adan, -aran, -bor, -born, -dir, -dor, -had, -ion, -las, -moth, -or, -phant, -phor, -randir, -ras, -rod, -rond, -ros, -thalion, -thir, -uil, and -we. Common prefixes are Adan-, Aeg-, Am-, Aran-, Bara-, Beleg-, Celeb-, Curu-, Dag-, El-, Fela-, Fin-, Gal-, Gil-, Hal-, Ing-, Lin-, Mal-, Pen-, Tar-, Thurin-, and Ul-.&lt;/li&gt;"/>
<label key="key:620757446:123856835" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Naming Guidelines: &lt;/rgb&gt;Hobbit-men of the Fallohide kindred usually take aristocratic-sounding names, drawing from the Frankish and Gothic languages. &#10;&#10;Some examples are Meriadoc, Odovacar, and Paladin. Common name endings are -acar, -ard, -bald, -bard, -brand, -bras, -come, -das, -dic, -doc, -egar, -fast, -fred, -gar, -gard, -grim, -ing, -lac, -las, -mac, -man, -mond, -nas, -red, -ric, -roc, -son, -wise. Common prefixes are Adel-, And-, Bando-, Dino-, Dod-, Ever-, Ferd-, Ferum-, Fortin-, Fred-, Gorma-, Hal-, Ham-, Hildi-, Hol-, Isen-, Isum-, Marma-, Meri-, Regin-, Sara-, Sere-, Tol-, and Wil-.&lt;/li&gt;"/>
<label key="key:620757446:127030227" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Naming Guidelines: &lt;/rgb&gt;With rare exception, the Elves of Middle-earth have Sindarin names.&#10;&#10;Names like Arwen, Celebrían, and Galadriel are examples of Elf-women in Middle-earth.&#10;&#10;Common feminine name endings in Sindarin are -anor, -dal, -dis, -el, -eth, -iel, -il, -gil, -los, -raen, -reth, -riel, -rian, -rien, -uilas, -uilos, -wen, and -wing. Common prefixes are Adan-, And-, Ar-, Bel-, Breg-, Celeb-, Dol-, Edhel-, El-, Fan-, Find-, Galadh-, Gil-, Hir-, Ior-, Ir-, Lal-, Mel-, Mor-, Nim-, Rod-, Sael-, and Tinu-.&lt;/li&gt;"/>
<label key="key:620757446:129265459" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Naming Guidelines: &lt;/rgb&gt;With rare exception, the Elves of Middle-earth have Sindarin names.&#10;&#10;Names like Elrond, Legolas, and Lindir are examples of Elf-men in Middle-earth.&#10;&#10;Common masculine name endings in Sindarin are -adan, -aran, -bor, -born, -dir, -dor, -had, -ion, -las, -moth, -or, -phant, -phor, -randir, -ras, -rod, -rond, -ros, -thalion, -thir, -uil, and -we. Common prefixes are Adan-, Aeg-, Am-, Aran-, Bara-, Beleg-, Celeb-, Curu-, Dag-, El-, Fela-, Fin-, Gal-, Gil-, Hal-, Ing-, Lin-, Mal-, Pen-, Tar-, Thurin-, and Ul-&lt;/li&gt;"/>
<label key="key:620757446:1339763" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Naming Guidelines: &lt;/rgb&gt;Hobbit-women are named after flowers or jewels.&#10;&#10;Examples of first names are Belladonna, Dora, Esmerelda, Lobelia, Ruby, Sapphire, and Tulip.&lt;/li&gt;"/>
<label key="key:620757446:137557923" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Naming Guidelines: &lt;/rgb&gt;Beornings take names influenced by Old Norse.&#10;&#10;Langhár, Ethild and Berafrith are examples of Beorning names.&#10;&#10;Common feminine name endings for Beornings are -a, -dis, -eith, -fast, -frith, -garth, -gifu, -gun, -hild, -la, -laug, -lin, -loth, -otta, -ny, -run, -thrith, -vi, and -vor. Common prefixes are Arin-, Bog-, Bera-, Birn-, Dis-, Dom-, Dyr-, Eir-, Esil-, Eth-, Ey-, Fast-, Feor-, Gerth-, Gis-, Gud-, Hall-, Har-, Hrim-, Huld-, Hun-, Ingi-, Jor-, Kat-, Is-, Lif-, Leot-, Mar-, Od-, Ol-, Ran-, Sal-, Sig-, Sol-, Svan-, Una-, and Vil-.&lt;/li&gt;"/>
<label key="key:620757446:138814947" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Naming Guidelines: &lt;/rgb&gt;Dwarves tend towards short, simple Norse-styled names.&#10;&#10;Common endings are -ori, -óin, -íli, -alin, -orin, -osi, -imli, and ormur, coupled with beginnings using consonants like D-, F-, G-, H-, K-, L-, M-, N-, R-, T-, Th-, and W-,  or paired consonants like Dr-, Dw-, Fl-, Gl-, or Thr-. Example are Dori, Glóin, Kíli, Balin, Thorin, Flosi, Gimli, and Gormur.&#10;&#10;A few dwarves have more complex names, combining whole words with specific endings or other whole words. (Examples: Skorgrím, Einskaldir.)&lt;/li&gt;"/>
<label key="key:620757446:13962563" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Lore: &lt;/rgb&gt;Driven from your home by death and war, you came to the hidden vale of Imladris, where you have long dwelt under Elrond's protection.&lt;/li&gt;"/>
<label key="key:620757446:151159187" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Lore: &lt;/rgb&gt;In Elder Days you dwelt in the fair Elf-lands of Beleriand, now broken and lost forever beneath the Sea.&lt;/li&gt;"/>
<label key="key:620757446:151958963" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Naming Guidelines: &lt;/rgb&gt;Stout-axe Dwarves have short, simple names in forms resembling old Baltic.&#10;&#10;Common endings are -a, -ad, -ag, -al, -as, -at, -ang, -el, -i, -ig, -ik, -ir, -o, -ok, -ot, -un, -ur, -ut, -uz. Examples include Khálik, Akád, Ilgo, Váruz, Kósi, Gúdag, Ságrok, Dávir, Ugél. Some also take Norse names like Longbeard Dwarves or old Slavonic like the Zhélruka."/>
<label key="key:620757446:154032899" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Naming Guidelines: &lt;/rgb&gt;Bree-men usually have short, simple English-styled names like Ned, Bill, Mat, Wil, or Tom, but longer or less familiar names -- such as Barliman, Humphrey, or Cuthbert -- are not unknown.&#10;&#10;Sometimes Bree-landers go by their last names, which are almost always related to plants, such as Appledore, Thistleway, Butterbur, or Ferny.&lt;/li&gt;"/>
<label key="key:620757446:160117843" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Naming Guidelines: &lt;/rgb&gt;With rare exceptions, the Men of Gondor have Sindarin names.&#10;&#10;Beregond, Boromir, and Faramir are examples of Gondor names.&#10;&#10;Common masculine name endings in Sindarin are -adan, -aran, -bor, -born, -dir, -dor, -had, -ion, -las, -or, -orn, -phant, -phor, -randir, -ras, -rod, -rond, -ros, -thelion, -thir, -uil, and -vorn, among others. Common prefixes are Adan-, Aeg-, Am-, Aran-, Bara-, Beleg-, Celeb-, Curu-, Dag-, El-, Fela-, Fin-, Gal-, Gil-, Hal-, Ing-, Lin-, Mal-, Pen-, Tar-, Thurin-, and Ul-.&lt;/li&gt;"/>
<label key="key:620757446:16377235" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Lore: &lt;/rgb&gt;Your home lies in the eastern wilds of Rhûn, a harsh land its people simply refer to as the Khôl. Its chieftains are loyal to Mordor, but some brave folk dare to resist Sauron's rule.&lt;/li&gt;"/>
<label key="key:620757446:167587923" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Naming Guidelines: &lt;/rgb&gt;The minions of Mordor almost always use the Black Speech, a language that is harsh and unpleasant to the ear.&#10;\Examples of Black Speech names and/or words are Ghash, Grishnakh, Lagduf, Lugburz, Mauhur, Muzgash, Sharku, Ufthak, and Ugluk.&lt;/li&gt;"/>
<label key="key:620757446:170492259" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Lore: &lt;/rgb&gt;Your home is in Ered Luin, the Blue Mountains, where there had once been two great dwarf-kingdoms and where the kinsmen of Thráin and his son Thorin Oakenshield lived in exile after Smaug drove them from the Lonely Mountain.&lt;/li&gt;"/>
<label key="key:620757446:171341779" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Naming Guidelines: &lt;/rgb&gt;With rare exception, the Elves of Middle-earth have Sindarin names.&#10;&#10;Names like Elrond, Legolas, and Lindir are examples of Elf-men in Middle-earth.&#10;&#10;Common masculine name endings in Sindarin are -adan, -aran, -bor, -born, -dir, -dor, -had, -ion, -las, -moth, -or, -phant, -phor, -randir, -ras, -rod, -rond, -ros, -thalion, -thir, -uil, and -we. Common prefixes are Adan-, Aeg-, Am-, Aran-, Bara-, Beleg-, Celeb-, Curu-, Dag-, El-, Fela-, Fin-, Gal-, Gil-, Hal-, Ing-, Lin-, Mal-, Pen-, Tar-, Thurin-, and Ul-.&lt;/li&gt;"/>
<label key="key:620757446:171983955" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Lore: &lt;/rgb&gt;You are from the region known as Near Harad but called Shagâna by its own people. Subjugated by the Great Empire of Ordâkh, the Shagâni are bidden to worship Sauron, but many defy this command.&lt;/li&gt;"/>
<label key="key:620757446:175009267" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Lore: &lt;/rgb&gt;You hail from Erebor, the Lonely Mountain, where Smaug the Golden made his lair until Thorin Oakenshield reclaimed it for his people. There does Dáin Ironfoot now rule as King under the Mountain.&lt;/li&gt;"/>
<label key="key:620757446:178773587" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Naming Guidelines: &lt;/rgb&gt;Dale-women tend to use Norse or Anglo-Saxon, such as Ethelhild, Beornwyn, Cynwise, or Leofwen.&#10;&#10;Some common name endings for Dale-women are -bur, -fled, -gifu, -leofu, -swith, -thryth, -waru, -wen, and -wyn, among others. Some very common prefixes are Elf-, Esc-, Ethel-, Beorn-, Ceo-, Cwen-, Cyn-, Ead-, Eal-, Here-, Leof-, and Wulf-.&lt;/li&gt;"/>
<label key="key:620757446:179721219" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Naming Guidelines: &lt;/rgb&gt;The Khôl is not a single nation but a land of many diverse peoples, from the raiders of Khûn and Jangova and the ruthless tribes of Sûha to the rich city-states that surround the inland sea. The Khôlar speak numerous languages, though many words are shared and names from one clan to the next are often similar.&#10;&#10;Examples: Ashakhi, Bermo, Darshama, Ergash, Fazila, Gulamaya, Ishtai, Jashura, Kharekhani, Nazokat, Olkunu, Rohati, Semokhai, Tufa, Yorgola.&lt;/li&gt;"/>
<label key="key:620757446:190938035" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Naming Guidelines: &lt;/rgb&gt;With rare exception, the Elves of Middle-earth have Sindarin names.&#10;&#10;Names like Arwen, Celebrían, and Galadriel are examples of Elf-women in Middle-earth.&#10;&#10;Common feminine name endings in Sindarin are -anor, -dal, -dis, -el, -eth, -iel, -il, -gil, -los, -raen, -reth, -riel, -rian, -rien, -uilas, -uilos, -wen, and -wing. Common prefixes are Adan-, And-, Ar-, Bel-, Breg-, Celeb-, Dol-, Edhel-, El-, Fan-, Find-, Galadh-, Gil-, Hir-, Ior-, Ir-, Lal-, Mel-, Mor-, Nim-, Rod-, Sael-, and Tinu-.&lt;/li&gt;"/>
<label key="key:620757446:194278995" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Naming Guidelines: &lt;/rgb&gt;With rare exception, the Elves of Middle-earth have Sindarin names.&#10;&#10;Names like Arwen, Celebrían, and Galadriel are examples of Elf-women in Middle-earth.&#10;&#10;Common feminine name endings in Sindarin are -anor, -dal, -dis, -el, -eth, -iel, -il, -gil, -los, -raen, -reth, -riel, -rian, -rien, -uilas, -uilos, -wen, and -wing. Common prefixes are Adan-, And-, Ar-, Bel-, Breg-, Celeb-, Dol-, Edhel-, El-, Fan-, Find-, Galadh-, Gil-, Hir-, Ior-, Ir-, Lal-, Mel-, Mor-, Nim-, Rod-, Sael-, and Tinu-.&lt;/li&gt;"/>
<label key="key:620757446:195508531" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Lore: &lt;/rgb&gt;You are one of the Horse-lords of the Riddermark, the realm granted to Eorl the Young by Cirion, Steward of Gondor, currently ruled by Théoden, son of Thengel.&lt;/li&gt;"/>
<label key="key:620757446:196767795" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Naming Guidelines: &lt;/rgb&gt;With rare exception, the Elves of Middle-earth have Sindarin names.&#10;&#10;Names like Elrond, Legolas, and Lindir are examples of Elf-men in Middle-earth.&#10;&#10;Common masculine name endings in Sindarin are -adan, -aran, -bor, -born, -dir, -dor, -had, -ion, -las, -moth, -or, -phant, -phor, -randir, -ras, -rod, -rond, -ros, -thalion, -thir, -uil, and -we. Common prefixes are Adan-, Aeg-, Am-, Aran-, Bara-, Beleg-, Celeb-, Curu-, Dag-, El-, Fela-, Fin-, Gal-, Gil-, Hal-, Ing-, Lin-, Mal-, Pen-, Tar-, Thurin-, and Ul-.&lt;/li&gt;"/>
<label key="key:620757446:199690163" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Lore: &lt;/rgb&gt;The Stoors were the last of the hobbit kindreds to come to the Shire, settling in the eastern marshlands that became known as the Marish. They generally tend to be heavier and broader of build than the other kindreds.&lt;/li&gt;"/>
<label key="key:620757446:200346115" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Naming Guidelines: &lt;/rgb&gt;With rare exception, the Elves of Middle-earth have Sindarin names.&#10;&#10;Names like Elrond, Legolas, and Lindir are examples of Elf-men in Middle-earth.&#10;&#10;Common masculine name endings in Sindarin are -adan, -aran, -bor, -born, -dir, -dor, -had, -ion, -las, -moth, -or, -phant, -phor, -randir, -ras, -rod, -rond, -ros, -thalion, -thir, -uil, and -we. Common prefixes are Adan-, Aeg-, Am-, Aran-, Bara-, Beleg-, Celeb-, Curu-, Dag-, El-, Fela-, Fin-, Gal-, Gil-, Hal-, Ing-, Lin-, Mal-, Pen-, Tar-, Thurin-, and Ul-.&lt;/li&gt;"/>
<label key="key:620757446:205283155" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Naming Guidelines: &lt;/rgb&gt;Hobbit-women are named after flowers or jewels.&#10;&#10;Examples of first names are Belladonna, Dora, Esmerelda, Lobelia, Ruby, Sapphire, and Tulip.&lt;/li&gt;"/>
<label key="key:620757446:206028819" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Lore: &lt;/rgb&gt;You come from Mordor, the realm of the Dark Lord Sauron. Growing in strength, he has returned to his fortress of Barad-dûr, calling all evil to him.&lt;/li&gt;"/>
<label key="key:620757446:207473683" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Lore: &lt;/rgb&gt;You hail from the land of Gondor, the South Kingdom once ruled jointly by the sons of Elendil, Isildur and Anárion, ever-watchful against the looming threat of Mordor.&lt;/li&gt;"/>
<label key="key:620757446:209366371" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Lore: &lt;/rgb&gt;You grew up in Bree-land, once part of the North Kingdom of Arnor, once ruled by Elendil the Tall as High King of Middle-earth, and later by his elder son Isildur. Now it is but a simple, rustic land, and the North Kingdom is no more.&lt;/li&gt;"/>
<label key="key:620757446:209641603" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Naming Guidelines: &lt;/rgb&gt;Bree-women tend towards simple, familiar English-styled names such as Ellie, Dora, Adela, and Clara, though less familiar names -- such as Amabel, Maribel, or Livina -- are not unknown.&#10;&#10;Sometimes Bree-landers go by their last names, which are almost always related to plants, such as Appledore, Thistleway, Butterbur, or Ferny.&lt;/li&gt;"/>
<label key="key:620757446:211677235" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Naming Guidelines: &lt;/rgb&gt;Hobbit-men of the Stoor kindred take either simple names ending in -o or aristocratic names drawing from the Frankish and Gothic languages.&#10;&#10;Common examples of first names would be Balbo, Drogo, Falco, Fredegar, Largo, Marmadoc, Mungo, Odo, Polo, Roderic, Wilcome.&lt;/li&gt;"/>
<label key="key:620757446:215879603" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Naming Guidelines: &lt;/rgb&gt;Men of the Rohirrim use Anglo-Saxon names, such as Éomer, Erkenbrand, and Théoden.&#10;&#10;Common name endings for men of the Rohirrim are -bryt, -dryt, -ea, -ferth, -frid, -frith, -gar, -helm, -here, -nath, -red, -ric, -rid, -sig, -stan, -thryth, -werd, -wald, -wig, -wine, and -wulf. Common prefixes for men of the Rohirrim are Ald-, An-, Beo-, Beort-, Beorn-, Cen-, Ceol-, Coen-, Cuth-, Ead-, Egel-, Elf-, Eo-, Esc-, Ethel-, Forth-, Frea-, Grim-, Guth-, Hes-, Ord-, and Theod-.&lt;/li&gt;"/>
<label key="key:620757446:22260147" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Naming Guidelines: &lt;/rgb&gt;With rare exception, the Elves of Middle-earth have Sindarin names.&#10;&#10;Names like Arwen, Celebrían, and Galadriel are examples of Elf-women in Middle-earth.&#10;&#10;Common feminine name endings in Sindarin are -anor, -dal, -dis, -el, -eth, -iel, -il, -gil, -los, -raen, -reth, -riel, -rian, -rien, -uilas, -uilos, -wen, and -wing. Common prefixes are Adan-, And-, Ar-, Bel-, Breg-, Celeb-, Dol-, Edhel-, El-, Fan-, Find-, Galadh-, Gil-, Hir-, Ior-, Ir-, Lal-, Mel-, Mor-, Nim-, Rod-, Sael-, and Tinu-.&lt;/li&gt;"/>
<label key="key:620757446:224354611" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Lore: &lt;/rgb&gt;Like all Beornings, you hail from the woods and dales surrounding the Anduin, from the shores near the Carrock up to the High Pass through the Misty Mountains.&lt;/li&gt;"/>
<label key="key:620757446:232669539" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Lore: &lt;/rgb&gt;You are from Ered Mithrin, the Grey Mountains, the chief of which is Mount Gundabad, from whence came Durin the Deathless, first Father of the Dwarves. Your kindred returned to the Mountains after the Dragons perished.&lt;/li&gt;"/>
<label key="key:620757446:234086131" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Lore: &lt;/rgb&gt;Dwelling among the dells of the Misty Mountains, the River Hobbits of Misthallow are a rustic folk, quick-tongued and nimble-fingered. Known mainly in old tales and songs, they seldom venture outside their secret vales.&lt;/li&gt;"/>
<label key="key:620757446:236596035" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Naming Guidelines: &lt;/rgb&gt;With rare exception, the Elves of Middle-earth have Sindarin names.&#10;&#10;Names like Elrond, Legolas, and Lindir are examples of Elf-men in Middle-earth.&#10;&#10;Common masculine name endings in Sindarin are -adan, -aran, -bor, -born, -dir, -dor, -had, -ion, -las, -moth, -or, -phant, -phor, -randir, -ras, -rod, -rond, -ros, -thalion, -thir, -uil, and -we. Common prefixes are Adan-, Aeg-, Am-, Aran-, Bara-, Beleg-, Celeb-, Curu-, Dag-, El-, Fela-, Fin-, Gal-, Gil-, Hal-, Ing-, Lin-, Mal-, Pen-, Tar-, Thurin-, and Ul-.&lt;/li&gt;"/>
<label key="key:620757446:236897331" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Naming Guidelines: &lt;/rgb&gt;With rare exception, the Elves of Middle-earth have Sindarin names.&#10;&#10;Names like Arwen, Celebrían, and Galadriel are examples of Elf-women in Middle-earth.&#10;&#10;Common feminine name endings in Sindarin are -anor, -dal, -dis, -el, -eth, -iel, -il, -gil, -los, -raen, -reth, -riel, -rian, -rien, -uilas, -uilos, -wen, and -wing. Common prefixes are Adan-, And-, Ar-, Bel-, Breg-, Celeb-, Dol-, Edhel-, El-, Fan-, Find-, Galadh-, Gil-, Hir-, Ior-, Ir-, Lal-, Mel-, Mor-, Nim-, Rod-, Sael-, and Tinu-.&lt;/li&gt;"/>
<label key="key:620757446:239353443" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Lore: &lt;/rgb&gt;You are of the Nandor of Edhellond, the great Elf-haven in the south built by Amroth upon the Bay of Belfalas.&lt;/li&gt;"/>
<label key="key:620757446:244221875" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Lore: &lt;/rgb&gt;Your home of Ossiriand survived the fall of Beleriand to become Gil-galad's realm of Lindon, now grown empty as the Elves depart for Valinor.&lt;/li&gt;"/>
<label key="key:620757446:245209379" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Naming Guidelines: &lt;/rgb&gt;Umbar's people come from all over Middle-earth, and their names are just as varied.&#10;&#10;Most Umbari have names in their own language (e.g., Arikam, Burax, Damonar, Erabek, Galkud, Hanomar, Ilcarix, Khelbas, Kurul, Melkhar, Namirek, Phamas, Sadux, Tazad, Ulam.)&#10;&#10;Others have names in Adûnaic (Aglarzar, Belgimil, Minalzagar, Rothkhor), Sindarin (Castion, Glador, Harndir, Maechanar), or the tongues of Harad (Kharuk, Mubujat, Olokhas, Tejukho).&lt;/li&gt;"/>
<label key="key:620757446:247044579" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Naming Guidelines: &lt;/rgb&gt;Hobbit-men of the Harfoot kindred usually take very simple names, ending in -o.&#10;&#10;Common examples of first names are Balbo, Bungo, Drogo, Falco, Fosco, Largo, Longo, Lotho, Mungo, Odo, Polo, and Ponto.&lt;/li&gt;"/>
<label key="key:620757446:253402099" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Naming Guidelines: &lt;/rgb&gt;Dwarves tend towards short, simple Norse-styled names.&#10;&#10;Common endings are -ori, -óin, -íli, -alin, -orin, -osi, -imli, and ormur, coupled with beginnings using consonants like D-, F-, G-, H-, K-, L-, M-, N-, R-, T-, Th-, and W-,  or paired consonants like Dr-, Dw-, Fl-, Gl-, or Thr-. Example are Dori, Glóin, Kíli, Balin, Thorin, Flosi, Gimli, and Gormur.&#10;&#10;A few dwarves have more complex names, combining whole words with specific endings or other whole words. (Examples: Skorgrím, Einskaldir.)&lt;/li&gt;"/>
<label key="key:620757446:256963875" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Naming Guidelines: &lt;/rgb&gt;Stout-axe Dwarves have short, simple names in forms resembling old Baltic.&#10;&#10;Common endings are -a, -ad, -ag, -al, -as, -at, -ang, -el, -i, -ig, -ik, -ir, -o, -ok, -ot, -un, -ur, -ut, -uz. Examples include Khálik, Akád, Ilgo, Váruz, Kósi, Gúdag, Ságrok, Dávir, Ugél. Some also take Norse names like Longbeard Dwarves or old Slavonic like the Zhélruka."/>
<label key="key:620757446:257914627" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Naming Guidelines: &lt;/rgb&gt;Dwarves tend towards short, simple Norse-styled names.&#10;&#10;Common endings are -ori, -óin, -íli, -alin, -orin, -osi, -imli, and ormur, coupled with beginnings using consonants like D-, F-, G-, H-, K-, L-, M-, N-, R-, T-, Th-, and W-,  or paired consonants like Dr-, Dw-, Fl-, Gl-, or Thr-. Example are Dori, Glóin, Kíli, Balin, Thorin, Flosi, Gimli, and Gormur.&#10;&#10;A few dwarves have more complex names, combining whole words with specific endings or other whole words. (Examples: Skorgrím, Einskaldir.)&lt;/li&gt;"/>
<label key="key:620757446:25828435" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Lore: &lt;/rgb&gt;You come from the Iron Hills, settled by dwarves as a refuge from the Cold-drakes, and whence came Dáin Ironfoot, King under the Mountain, kinsman of the great Thorin Oakenshield.&lt;/li&gt;"/>
<label key="key:620757446:261165955" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Lore: &lt;/rgb&gt;You are from the south-western halls of Ered Nimrais, the White Mountains in the south bordering the lands of Andrast. Though your kingdom lies far from the central mountains where Men once dwelt, the rumour of the Oathbreakers has given your realm an ill name.&lt;/li&gt;"/>
<label key="key:620757446:26207891" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Naming Guidelines: &lt;/rgb&gt;With rare exception, the Elves of Middle-earth have Sindarin names.&#10;&#10;Names like Arwen, Celebrían, and Galadriel are examples of Elf-women in Middle-earth.&#10;&#10;Common feminine name endings in Sindarin are -anor, -dal, -dis, -el, -eth, -iel, -il, -gil, -los, -raen, -reth, -riel, -rian, -rien, -uilas, -uilos, -wen, and -wing. Common prefixes are Adan-, And-, Ar-, Bel-, Breg-, Celeb-, Dol-, Edhel-, El-, Fan-, Find-, Galadh-, Gil-, Hir-, Ior-, Ir-, Lal-, Mel-, Mor-, Nim-, Rod-, Sael-, and Tinu-.&lt;/li&gt;"/>
<label key="key:620757446:265962291" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Lore: &lt;/rgb&gt;You are a Stout-axe, a Dwarf of the Khirvísa clan, in thrall to the Dark Lord of Mordor.&#10;&#10;Stripped of your history, your clan name, and even your own language, the Stout-axes have become a lost people, with each generation growing stronger and grimmer than the last as ceaseless labour and suffering reshapes them. As Mordor grows in might, the Enemy has put the Stout-axes to ever more dangerous work in the furnaces of Udûn and beneath Barad-dûr itself, heedless of how many lives are spent as he musters his armies for War.&lt;/li&gt;"/>
<label key="key:620757446:267701267" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Naming Guidelines: &lt;/rgb&gt;The Shagâni hail from many different vassal lands, descended from such fabled realms as Hamât, Nísaka, and the city-state of Zajâna. Its people are varied and accustomed to war and hardship.&#10;&#10;Their names are similarly varied, having blended many tongues into a single Shagâni language.&#10;&#10;Examples: Arad, Baghi, Dudan, Etak, Harash, Janabor, Kurajud, Khetag, Meghaf, Nirekh, Rokhmar, Sepethut, Thakur, Udakhir, Zanukh.&lt;/li&gt;"/>
<label key="key:620757446:28202163" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Lore: &lt;/rgb&gt;You are a Wood-elf of Mirkwood, once called Greenwood the Great, where King Thranduil keeps watch against the growing darkness of Dol Guldur, former stronghold of Sauron in his guise as the Necromancer.&lt;/li&gt;"/>
<label key="key:620757446:36917667" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Lore: &lt;/rgb&gt;Lovers of trees and woodlands, the Fallohides were the first hobbits to come to the Shire. They generally tend to be fairer of skin and hair, as well as taller and more slender.&lt;/li&gt;"/>
<label key="key:620757446:3972979" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Naming Guidelines: &lt;/rgb&gt;Umbar's people come from all over Middle-earth, and their names are just as varied.&#10;&#10;Most Umbari have names in their own language (e.g., Adasi, Balaza, Damikh, Egini, Galamira, Hengali, Jatimaga, Kashuri, Luga, Matani, Nurgud, Pishadi, Shalmakh, Tukuli, Urutu).&#10;&#10;Others have names in Adûnaic (Aphanari, Imraphel, Lomikali, Pharazin), Sindarin (Falassiel, Gelwen, Merenil, Oreleth), or the tongues of Harad (Arnatha, Khujun, Nurmado, Rajondi).&lt;/li&gt;"/>
<label key="key:620757446:40057987" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Lore: &lt;/rgb&gt;The memory of the white towers of Gondolin, hidden city of the High Elves, still burns within you, though it fell to treachery long ago.&lt;/li&gt;"/>
<label key="key:620757446:41550931" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Naming Guidelines: &lt;/rgb&gt;With rare exception, the Elves of Middle-earth have Sindarin names.&#10;&#10;Names like Arwen, Celebrían, and Galadriel are examples of Elf-women in Middle-earth.&#10;&#10;Common feminine name endings in Sindarin are -anor, -dal, -dis, -el, -eth, -iel, -il, -gil, -los, -raen, -reth, -riel, -rian, -rien, -uilas, -uilos, -wen, and -wing. Common prefixes are Adan-, And-, Ar-, Bel-, Breg-, Celeb-, Dol-, Edhel-, El-, Fan-, Find-, Galadh-, Gil-, Hir-, Ior-, Ir-, Lal-, Mel-, Mor-, Nim-, Rod-, Sael-, and Tinu-.&lt;/li&gt;"/>
<label key="key:620757446:41992371" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Lore: &lt;/rgb&gt;You come from Lothlórien, the fabled golden woods whose Elves dwell high in the mallorn-trees and are ruled by Celeborn, wisest of the Eldar of Middle-earth, and the Lady Galadriel.&lt;/li&gt;"/>
<label key="key:620757446:44114963" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Naming Guidelines: &lt;/rgb&gt;Dwarves tend towards short, simple Norse-styled names.&#10;&#10;Common endings are -ori, -óin, -íli, -alin, -orin, -osi, -imli, and ormur, coupled with beginnings using consonants like D-, F-, G-, H-, K-, L-, M-, N-, R-, T-, Th-, and W-,  or paired consonants like Dr-, Dw-, Fl-, Gl-, or Thr-. Example are Dori, Glóin, Kíli, Balin, Thorin, Flosi, Gimli, and Gormur.&#10;&#10;A few dwarves have more complex names, combining whole words with specific endings or other whole words. (Examples: Skorgrím, Einskaldir.)&lt;/li&gt;"/>
<label key="key:620757446:47889203" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Naming Guidelines: &lt;/rgb&gt;With rare exception, the Elves of Middle-earth have Sindarin names.&#10;&#10;Names like Elrond, Legolas, and Lindir are examples of Elf-men in Middle-earth.&#10;&#10;Common masculine name endings in Sindarin are -adan, -aran, -bor, -born, -dir, -dor, -had, -ion, -las, -moth, -or, -phant, -phor, -randir, -ras, -rod, -rond, -ros, -thalion, -thir, -uil, and -we. Common prefixes are Adan-, Aeg-, Am-, Aran-, Bara-, Beleg-, Celeb-, Curu-, Dag-, El-, Fela-, Fin-, Gal-, Gil-, Hal-, Ing-, Lin-, Mal-, Pen-, Tar-, Thurin-, and Ul-.&lt;/li&gt;"/>
<label key="key:620757446:61096611" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Lore: &lt;/rgb&gt;You hail from Imladris, called Rivendell by Men, built by Elrond Halfelven as a refuge for the Elves of Eregion as they fled destruction at the hands of Sauron.&lt;/li&gt;"/>
<label key="key:620757446:62890579" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Naming Guidelines: &lt;/rgb&gt;Dale-men tend to use Norse or Anglo-Saxon names, such as Bard, Brand, Eadald, and Hengest.&#10;&#10;Some common name endings for Dale-men are -bryt, -dryt, -ea, -ferth, -frid, -frith, -gar, -helm, -here, -laf, -nath, -red, -ric, -rid, -sig, -stan, -thryth, -werd, -wald, -wig, -wine, and -wulf. Some common prefixes for Dale-men are Ald-, An-, Beo-, Beorht-, Beorn-, Cen-, Ceol-, Cuth-, Ead-, Egel-, Elf-, Esc-, Ethel-, Forth-, Frea-, Grim-, Guth-, Hes-, Ord-, and Theod-.&lt;/li&gt;"/>
<label key="key:620757446:73575107" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Naming Guidelines: &lt;/rgb&gt;Hobbit-women are named after flowers or jewels.&#10;&#10;Examples of first names are Belladonna, Dora, Esmerelda, Lobelia, Ruby, Sapphire, and Tulip.&lt;/li&gt;"/>
<label key="key:620757446:76122867" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Naming Guidelines: &lt;/rgb&gt;With rare exception, the Elves of Middle-earth have Sindarin names.&#10;&#10;Names like Arwen, Celebrían, and Galadriel are examples of Elf-women in Middle-earth.&#10;&#10;Common feminine name endings in Sindarin are -anor, -dal, -dis, -el, -eth, -iel, -il, -gil, -los, -raen, -reth, -riel, -rian, -rien, -uilas, -uilos, -wen, and -wing. Common prefixes are Adan-, And-, Ar-, Bel-, Breg-, Celeb-, Dol-, Edhel-, El-, Fan-, Find-, Galadh-, Gil-, Hir-, Ior-, Ir-, Lal-, Mel-, Mor-, Nim-, Rod-, Sael-, and Tinu-.&lt;/li&gt;"/>
<label key="key:620757446:80787139" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Naming Guidelines: &lt;/rgb&gt;With rare exception, the Elves of Middle-earth have Sindarin names.&#10;&#10;Names like Elrond, Legolas, and Lindir are examples of Elf-men in Middle-earth.&#10;&#10;Common masculine name endings in Sindarin are -adan, -aran, -bor, -born, -dir, -dor, -had, -ion, -las, -moth, -or, -phant, -phor, -randir, -ras, -rod, -rond, -ros, -thalion, -thir, -uil, and -we. Common prefixes are Adan-, Aeg-, Am-, Aran-, Bara-, Beleg-, Celeb-, Curu-, Dag-, El-, Fela-, Fin-, Gal-, Gil-, Hal-, Ing-, Lin-, Mal-, Pen-, Tar-, Thurin-, and Ul-.&lt;/li&gt;"/>
<label key="key:620757446:82786051" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Naming Guidelines: &lt;/rgb&gt;River Hobbit women still use the olden names of their kind, drawing on ancient Celtic and Germanic tongues.&#10;&#10;Some examples are Angharad, Clotild, Irmingard, Odilia, and Rosyn. Common name endings are -ban, -berga, -bryn, -dis, -dolen, -drud, -ed, -eri, -flad, -gara, -gund, -hith, -ian, -lag, -lind, -rid, -switha, -thryth, -weth,  and -wyn. Coommon prefixes are Adal-, Amal-, Anar-, Auda-, Blod-, Brun-, Cara-, Cin-, Dil-, Dun-, Ead-, El-, Fion-, Fritha-, Glad-, Glyn-, Gwen-, Haf-, Hele-, Léof-, Luda-, Mair-, Mild-, Ragen-, Rhian-, Ros-, Sera-, Tara-, and Wili-.&lt;/li&gt;"/>
<label key="key:620757446:8432643" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Lore: &lt;/rgb&gt;You hail from Lindon, the green lands of the Elves between Ered Luin and the Sea, where Gil-galad, the last great Elf-king, once ruled. Círdan the Shipwright now rules there from Mithlond, the Grey Havens.&lt;/li&gt;"/>
<label key="key:620757446:89232019" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Naming Guidelines: &lt;/rgb&gt;The Shagâni hail from many different vassal lands, descended from such fabled realms as Hamât, Nísaka, and the city-state of Zajâna. Its people are varied and accustomed to war and hardship.&#10;&#10;Their names are similarly varied, having blended many tongues into a single Shagâni language.&#10;&#10;Examples: Akhada, Biruli, Etasha, Ganar, Hikani, Jukara, Khusi, Karuna, Labama, Mukibi, Nikara, Ritri, Sayu, Tajaba, Zisha.&lt;/li&gt;"/>
<label key="key:620757446:91036979" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Lore: &lt;/rgb&gt;You spent your younger days in the cavern-fortress of Nargothrond, the hall of Finrod Felagund, whose beauty was lost in the wars of old.&lt;/li&gt;"/>
<label key="key:620757446:9105843" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Naming Guidelines: &lt;/rgb&gt;Women of the Rohirrim use such names as Beornwyn, Cynwise, Éowyn, or Léofwen.&#10;&#10;Some common name endings for women of the Rohirrim are -bur, -fled, -gifu, -leofu, -swith, -thryth, -waru, -wen, and -wyn. Common prefixes among the women of the Rohirrim are Elf-, Esc-, Ethel-, Beorn-, Ceo-, Cwen-, Cyn-, Ead-, Eal-, Eo-, Here-, Leof-, and Wulf-.&lt;/li&gt;"/>
<label key="key:620757446:93024147" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Lore: &lt;/rgb&gt;The Harfoots are the most prodigious hole-dwellers and were the first to cross west into Eriador. They generally tend to be browner of skin than the other kindreds, as well as smaller and shorter.&lt;/li&gt;"/>
<label key="key:620757446:95359955" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Naming Guidelines: &lt;/rgb&gt;The Khôl is not a single nation but a land of many diverse peoples, from the raiders of Khûn and Jangova and the ruthless tribes of Sûha to the rich city-states that surround the inland sea. The Khôlar speak numerous languages, though many words are shared and names from one clan to the next are often similar.&#10;&#10;Examples: Akhil, Baludam, Gozal, Hurmat, Jangador, Khashar, Kulkoz, Muhidur, Nurbakhun, Otish, Shereg, Tezarek, Uskir, Yashin, Zoharidash.&lt;/li&gt;"/>
<label key="key:620757446:95704163" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Naming Guidelines: &lt;/rgb&gt;With rare exception, the Elves of Middle-earth have Sindarin names.&#10;&#10;Names like Elrond, Legolas, and Lindir are examples of Elf-men in Middle-earth.&#10;&#10;Common masculine name endings in Sindarin are -adan, -aran, -bor, -born, -dir, -dor, -had, -ion, -las, -moth, -or, -phant, -phor, -randir, -ras, -rod, -rond, -ros, -thalion, -thir, -uil, and -we. Common prefixes are Adan-, Aeg-, Am-, Aran-, Bara-, Beleg-, Celeb-, Curu-, Dag-, El-, Fela-, Fin-, Gal-, Gil-, Hal-, Ing-, Lin-, Mal-, Pen-, Tar-, Thurin-, and Ul-.&lt;/li&gt;"/>
<label key="key:620757446:98400851" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Naming Guidelines: &lt;/rgb&gt;With rare exception, the Elves of Middle-earth have Sindarin names.&#10;&#10;Names like Arwen, Celebrían, and Galadriel are examples of Elf-women in Middle-earth.&#10;&#10;Common feminine name endings in Sindarin are -anor, -dal, -dis, -el, -eth, -iel, -il, -gil, -los, -raen, -reth, -riel, -rian, -rien, -uilas, -uilos, -wen, and -wing. Common prefixes are Adan-, And-, Ar-, Bel-, Breg-, Celeb-, Dol-, Edhel-, El-, Fan-, Find-, Galadh-, Gil-, Hir-, Ior-, Ir-, Lal-, Mel-, Mor-, Nim-, Rod-, Sael-, and Tinu-.&lt;/li&gt;"/>
<label key="key:620757446:99053395" value="&lt;li&gt;&lt;rgb=#FFFF00&gt;Lore: &lt;/rgb&gt;You hail from Umbar, once a wealthy trading port and now home to the dreaded Corsairs. Its current rulers worship Sauron, but its people still yearn for freedom.&lt;/li&gt;"/>
</labels>
